A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (A-K) FA1783
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Community and National Initiatives, 1999-2019; 1; 25.44 Cubic Feet 67 letter document boxes
  - Community Foundation of Grand Forks, East Grand Forks, and Region - Supplemental Grant (2009-0263), 2009-2016 (Box 33, Folder 449-450)
  - Community Foundation of Greater Fort Wayne - Supplemental Grant (2009-0261), 2009-2011 (Box 33, Folder 451-452)
  - Community Foundation of North Florida - Endowment Giving Day Initiative (2015-50588) (Box 33, Folder 456)
  - Community Foundation of North Florida - Online Giving Technologies (2012-0334) (Box 34, Folder 457)
  - Community Foundation in Jacksonville - Public School Funding Tracker, Knight Community Information Challenge (2012-0155), 2010-2013 (Box 34, Folder 458)
  - Community Foundation of the Chattahoochee Valley Inc. - On the Table Columbus (2017-53756) (Box 34, Folder 459)
  - Community Foundation of the Chattahoochee Valley Inc. - Evolving MidTown: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52491) (Box 34, Folder 460)
  - Community Foundation of the Chattahoochee Valley Inc. - Giving Day Initiative, Columbus (2013-46678), 2011-2014 (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Community Foundation of the Chattahoochee Valley Inc. - Supplemental Grant (2009-0258), 2009-2016 (Box 34, Folder 462-463)
  - Community Foundation Serving Boulder County - 2017 Knight Community Information Lab Winner (2017-54658) (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Community Foundation Serving Boulder County - Culture of Giving (2015-50750) (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - Community Foundation Serving Boulder County - A Midsummer Night's Dream by Ten Thousand Things Theatre, St. Paul (2009-0254), 2009-2013 (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - Community Foundation Silicon Valley - Annual Showcase of South Bay Performing Arts Organizations (2004-0275), 2004-2006 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Community Partnership, Inc. - Civic Health (2017-55309) (Box 35, Folder 472)
  - Connect to Compete, Inc. - Connect2Compete (2012-0231), 2012-2014 (Box 35, Folder 478-480)
    Coalition to make internet services, equipment, and training affordable and compelling for low-income families, with a focus on Knight communities.
  - Conservancy for Cuyahoga Valley National Park - First Mountain Bike Trail (2014-50077), 2014-2015 (Box 36, Folder 482)
  - Contexto LLC - Miami by Design (2015-50825), 2013-2015 (Box 36, Folder 483)
  - Corktown Community Development Fund - FBO Roosevelt Park Conservancy: Roosevelt Park Concession Design-Build (2014-48660), 2011-2014 (Box 36, Folder 490)
  - Cornetta Lane - Pedal to Porch: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52498), 2013-2016 (Box 36, Folder 491)
  - The Corporation of Mercer University - Mercer Music at Capricorn Interpretive Plan (2017-54551) (Box 36, Folder 495)
  - Corporation of Mercer University - Knight Center for Collaborative Journalism (2011-0362), 2010-2016 (Box 37, Folder 498-499)
  - Council on Foundations - Centennial Fall Conference for Community Foundations (2014-49400) (Box 37, Folder 507)
  - Council of Friends Groups of Akron Summit County Public Library Inc. - Micro Business Center (2014-50264), 2013-2014 (Box 37, Folder 510)
  - County of Summit Auditor - Code for America, Interactive Website on Hiking, Bicycling, and Water Trails (2012-0359), 2011-2013 (Box 38, Folder 513)
  - Crain's Detroit Business - Detroit Homecoming: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50674), 2013-2015 (Box 38, Folder 514)
  - Creative Enterprise Zone - Window Into the Creative Enterprise Zone (2016-53185), 2014-2016 (Box 38, Folder 518)
  - Cuba Study Group, Inc. - Cuba Entrepreneurship Series (2014-48094), 2012-2014 (Box 39, Folder 529)
  - Cuyahoga Valley Countryside Conservancy - Farmers' Market Placemaking (2017-54302) (Box 39, Folder 536)
  - Cycles for Change - Slow Roll St. Paul (2017-54605) (Box 39, Folder 537)
  - Cycles for Change - Slow Roll Twin Cities (2016-52773) (Box 39, Folder 538)
  - CVOX Group LLC - Fintech LATAM (2014-49295), 2012-2014 (Box 39, Folder 539)
  - Dade Legal Aid - Venture Law Project (VLP) Legal Services for Start-Ups (2013-45766), 2012-2014 (Box 39, Folder 540)
  - Delaware River Waterfront Corporation - Cherry Street Pier (2016-53727), 2014-2016 (Box 40, Folder 552)
  - Delta Institute - Steel City Salvage: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52500), 2015-2017 (Box 40, Folder 554)
  - Detroit 300 Conservancy - Downtown Placemaking Expansion (2014-49250), 2012-2014 (Box 41, Folder 560)
  - Detroit Area Pre-College Engineering Program - Expanding Opportunity in Detroit with the Assistance of Design Thinking (2016-52373) (Box 41, Folder 561)
  - Detroit Bike City, Inc. - Detroit's Slow Roll: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54213) (Box 41, Folder 562)
  - Detroit Creative Corridor Center - Passenger Center (2014-48636), 1999-2014 (Box 41, Folder 563)
    Residency for emerging creative practitioners in Detroit's Capital Park District.
  - Detroit Development Fund - Entrepreneurial Place-Based Lending Program (2013-45985), 2011-2013 (Box 41, Folder 564)
  - Detroit Economic Growth Association - The Buzz: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50658), 2012-2015 (Box 41, Folder 565)
    Transform vacant lots through design workshops that partner barbers with landscape contractors to develop new mowing and pattern-making techniques helping to combat blight and attract and retain talent in the city.
  - Detroit Economic Growth Association - Motor City Match (2015-50963), 2012-2017 (Box 41, Folder 566)
  - Detroit Future City - 139 Square Miles: A Detroit Data Report (2017-54158) (Box 41, Folder 570)
  - Detroit Riverfront Conservancy - Atwater Beach: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54207) (Box 41, Folder 574)
  - Detroit Riverfront Conservancy - Dequindre Cut Market: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52495), 2013-2016 (Box 42, Folder 575)
  - Detroit Riverfront Conservancy - Riverfront Development (2015-51687), 2013-2015 (Box 42, Folder 576)
  - Detroit Riverfront Conservancy - River Days Artscape Art Competition (2012-0251), 2012-2013 (Box 42, Folder 577)
  - Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall, Inc. - Summer Riverfront Home (2007-0241), 2006-2008 (Box 42, Folder 582)
  - Detroit Development Fund - Shorebank Enterprise (2006-0181), 2010-2017 (Box 42, Folder 583-584, Box 43, Folder 585)
  - Digital Grass - Innovation and Technology Changing the Narrative (2016-53485) (Box 43, Folder 588)
  - Digital Grass - Innovation and Technology (2014-49892), 2014-2015 (Box 43, Folder 589)
  - Digital Public Library of America (Open Knowledge Commons) - Inclusion of Knight-Community Libraries (2012-0232), 2010-2013 (Box 43, Folder 592)
  - Donell Meadows Institute - Leverage Points Visualization for Civic Innovators (2014-48405) (Box 44, Folder 598)
  - DonorsChoose.org - Gift Cards for Florida Philanthropic Network Summit (2014-48006), 2011-2014 (Box 44, Folder 600)
  - DonorsChoose.org - Gift Cards for Florida Philanthropic Network Summit (2014-49767) (Box 44, Folder 601)
  - Do Something, Inc. - SMS Platform Expansion (2014-48182), 2013-2016 (Box 44, Folder 602)
  - Downtown Akron Partnership Inc. - Downtown Akron Partnership 2017 (2017-54256), 2016-2017 (Box 44, Folder 607)
  - Downtown Akron Partnership Inc. - Public Space Public Life Survey (2016-52996), 2014-2016 (Box 44, Folder 608)
  - Downtown Detroit Partnership Inc. - Detroit Homecoming (2017-54656) (Box 44, Folder 610)
  - Downtown Detroit Partnership Inc. - Neighborhood Storytelling and Tour Strategies for Civic Exchange (2017-54997) (Box 44, Folder 611)
  - Downtown Detroit Partnership Inc. - Detroit's Spirit Plaza (2017-54537) (Box 44, Folder 612)
  - Downtown Detroit Partnership Inc. - Mobility and Economic Opportunity Model (2016-52125), 2013-2017 (Box 44, Folder 613)
  - Downtown Detroit Partnership Inc. - LIVE Detroit: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50641) (Box 44, Folder 614)
  - Drexel University - Leading for Change Fellowship (2016-53718) (Box 45, Folder 615)
  - Drexel University - Urban Innovation Summit and Fellowship (2017-54987) (Box 45, Folder 616)
  - Duluth-Superior Area Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant (2009-0260), 2009-2016 (Box 45, Folder 621-622)
  - Early Childhood Initiative Foundation - Children's Movement Digital Strategy Expansion (2017-54822) (Box 45, Folder 623)
  - EarlyWorks LLC - Planning for Vision 2021 (2017-54575) (Box 45, Folder 625)
  - EarlyWorks LLC - Detroit Women's Leadership Network (2016-53398), 2013-2016 (Box 45, Folder 626)
  - Eastern Market Corporation - Murals in the Market Public Event (2016-52883) (Box 46, Folder 628)
  - Eastern Market Corporation - Public Space Enhancement (2015-51690) (Box 46, Folder 629)
  - EcoTech Visions Foundation - The Future of Green (2015-51487), 2014-2017 (Box 46, Folder 630)
  - Emerson College - Towards a Civic Framework for Smart Cities (2017-54721) (Box 46, Folder 636)
  - Emerson College - Organizations vs. Civic Technologies (2014-47946), 2011-2014 (Box 46, Folder 637)
  - Emerson College - Community-Driven Technology Programs, Knight Grantees-Harvard Kennedy School Collaboration (2012-2327), 2010-2013 (Box 46, Folder 638)
  - Emerson College - Community PlanIT (2011-0358), 2010-2012 (Box 46, Folder 639)
  - Endeavor Global, Inc. - Building an Entrepreneurship Ecosystem in the Twin Cities (2016-52981) (Box 46, Folder 641)
  - Endeavor Initiative Inc. - Endeavor Miami (2012-0350), 2010-2016 (Box 47, Folder 642)
  - Endeavor Miami - Endeavor Miami Gala 2016 (2016-53364) (Box 47, Folder 643)
  - Endeavor Miami - Endeavor International Selection Panel Miami (2014-50105), 2013-2014 (Box 47, Folder 644)
  - Endeavor Miami - Annual Gala (2015-51742) (Box 47, Folder 645)
  - Enterprise Development Corporation of South Florida - Miami Entrepreneurial Support Program (2013-46777) (Box 47, Folder 646)
  - EP Enterprises LLC - Miami Caribbean Code (MC2) Phase 1: Youth Summit (2014-49396) (Box 47, Folder 647)
  - The Everglades Foundation, Inc. - George Barley Water Prize (2015-51819), 2013-2015 (Box 47, Folder 652)
  - Exhibition District - Local Color: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54397) (Box 47, Folder 654)
  - Facts about Cuban Exiles - FACE in Spanish (2013-48287), 2011-2013 (Box 48, Folder 658)
  - Fairmount Park Conservancy - Public Spaces to Create a Culture of Engagement (2016-53525), 2015-2017 (Box 48, Folder 660)
  - Fairmount Park Conservancy - Civic Commons Storytelling: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50567), 2012-2016 (Box 48, Folder 661)
  - Fairmount Park Conservancy - Civic Commons Storytelling (2015-50567), 2012-2016 (Box 48, Folder 662)
  - Fairmount Park Conservancy - Sensor Technology to Gauge the Impact of Reimagining the Civic Commons (2015-51811), 2013-2016 (Box 48, Folder 663)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Carolina Civic Theatre (2014-49906), 2012-2017 (Box 48, Folder 664)
  - Fastrack Institute Inc. - Miami Mobility Fastrack (2017-54123) (Box 48, Folder 666)
  - Fedcap Rehabilitative Services, Inc. - ReServe Miami (2013-46971), 2011-2013 (Box 48, Folder 667)
    Connecting nonprofits and public institutions with experienced professionals who are 55 years of age or older who want to give back to their communities in part-time job opportunities.
  - Feverish Holdings - Code Fever (2013-46954), 2013-2014 (Box 48, Folder 669)
  - Florida East Coast Industries, LLC - Ludlam Trail Master Plan (2015-51892), 2013-2015 (Box 49, Folder 677)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - The FIU, Miami Urban Future Initiative (2017-53791), 2014-2017 (Box 49, Folder 680)
  - Florida International University - Rokk3r Lab/MakerBot Innovation Lab (2015-50560) (Box 49, Folder 682)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - Power of Design Fest (2013-46798), 2012-2014 (Box 49, Folder 684)
  - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - Preparing Miami for Democratic Transition in Cuba (2013-47032), 2012-2016 (Box 49, Folder 685)
  - Florida International University - Miami Urban Neighborhood Building Studio (2013-47255), 2011-2014 (Box 49, Folder 687)
  - Florida Venture Forum - Florida Capital Conference (2014-49654) (Box 50, Folder 695)
  - The Food Trust - Expanding Night Market Philadelphia (2014-48943), 2014-2016 (Box 50, Folder 696)
  - The Food Trust - Expanding Night Market Philadelphia (2016-53729) (Box 50, Folder 697)
  - Foundation for Detroit's Future - Support Detroit's Plan of Adjustment (2014-49519), 2014-2016 (Box 51, Folder 705-706)
  - Foundation for Public Broadcasting in Georgia - Knight Center for Collaborative Journalism, Mercer University (2011-0363), 2010-2015 (Box 51, Folder 709-710)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Charlotte Mecklenburg Opportunity Task Force (2017-53743) (Box 51, Folder 711)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - On the Table Charlotte (2017-53759) (Box 51, Folder 712)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Civic Theater Goes Digital (2015-51686), 2014-2016 (Box 51, Folder 713)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - North Tyron Vision and Master Planning Process (2014-48039) (Box 51, Folder 714)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Carolina Civic Theater (2014-49906), 2012-2015 (Box 51, Folder 716)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Project L.I.F.T. (2012-0122), 2009-2016 (Box 52, Folder 718-719)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Project L.I.F.T. (2012-0123), 2010-2016 (Box 52, Folder 720)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas - Charlotte Housing Authority Scholarship Endowment (2005-0219), 2003-2005 (Box 52, Folder 724)
  - The Foundation of the University of North Carolina at Charlotte, Inc. - A Pop-Up Public Space (2014-49176), 2012-2016 (Box 53, Folder 727)
  - Frameworks Institute - A New Narrative for Economic Integration (2015-50703), 2013-2015 (Box 53, Folder 732)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia Foundation - Catalyzing Community Creativity and Innovation (2017-54831) (Box 53, Folder 736)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia - Read by 4th Summer Programming (2016-52638) (Box 53, Folder 737)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia - Art in 21st Century Libraries (2013-46993), 2012-2013 (Box 53, Folder 739)
  - Friends Council on Education - Planning for the Re-Opening of the Friends School District (2016-53508) (Box 54, Folder 744)
  - Friends of the Underline, Inc. - Brickell Backyard: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2015-52507), 2014-2016 (Box 54, Folder 750)
  - Friends of the Underline, Inc. - Underline Master Plan (2014-49961), 2014-2015 (Box 54, Folder 751)
  - Fund for Our Economic Future - Akron Growth and Opportunity Initiative (2013-46596), 2012-2016 (Box 55, Folder 754)
  - Fund for Our Economic Future - Regional Philanthropic Collaboration (2010-0292), 2010-2013 (Box 55, Folder 755)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - PHL Participatory Design Lab: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54442), 2015-2017 (Box 55, Folder 756)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - City of Philadelphia Civic Engagement Program (2016-52891) (Box 55, Folder 757)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - Citymart (2015-50815), 2013-2015 (Box 55, Folder 758)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - The Classics Return to Dell East (2014-49206) (Box 55, Folder 759)
  - Fund for Philadelphia - Parks and Recreation Public Spaces Special Events Permitting Reform (2016-52803) (Box 55, Folder 760)
  - Funders' Network for Smart Growth and Livable Communities, Inc. - Membership and General Support (2017-55194) (Box 55, Folder 764)
  - Funders' Network for Smart Growth and Livable Communities, Inc. - The Funders' Network Annual Conference in St. Paul (2016-53227) (Box 55, Folder 765)
  - Funders' Network for Smart Growth and Livable Communities, Inc. - Three Year Membership (2014-49116), 2012-2014 (Box 55, Folder 766)
  - Fund for the School District of Philadelphia - Millenial Retention through Quality Public Schools (2015-50606), 2012-2015 (Box 56, Folder 768)
  - Fusion Media Network, LLC - Fusion Sandbox (2014-48930), 2013-2016 (Box 56, Folder 769)
  - Garden to Table Silicon Valley - Taylor Street Farm (2015-51568) (Box 56, Folder 771)
  - Gehl Studio, Inc. - San Jose Public Life Project (2017-54613) (Box 56, Folder 772)
  - Gehl.org, Inc. - Gehl Institute Movement Building (2016-52233), 2016-2017 (Box 56, Folder 773)
  - Gehl.org, Inc. - Public Space Public Life (2015-50465), 2015-2016 (Box 56, Folder 774)
  - Gehl.org, Inc. - Making the West End More Mobile (2015-51001) (Box 56, Folder 775)
  - Georgia Crowdfund, Inc. - Small Business Day (2017-55306) (Box 57, Folder 780)
  - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation - New Jersey News Ecosystem: A 2016 Knight Community Information Challenge Investment (2016-53247), 2016-2017 (Box 57, Folder 784)
  - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation - Building a New Jersey News Ecosystem (2014-48594), 2014-2015 (Box 57, Folder 785)
  - Girls Who Code, Inc. - Summer Immersion Programs (2015-50746), 2013-2017 (Box 57, Folder 787)
  - GiveMN - Everyday Giving on GiveMN (2015-50795) (Box 57, Folder 788)
  - GiveMN - Giving Day Initiative, St. Paul (2013-46760), 2011-2014 (Box 57, Folder 790)
  - Global Detroit - Economic Development Initiative (2013-47944), 2013-2016 (Box 57, Folder 792)
  - GoodCompany - Group Curriculum Refinement (2013-46864), 2012-2013 (Box 58, Folder 799)
  - Goodwill Industries of Southern Piedmont - Job Skills Training, Queens University (2013-45839), 2011-2013 (Box 58, Folder 801)
  - Grameen America, Inc. - Financially Empowering Low-Income Women through Microfinance (2016-53126), 2016-2017 (Box 58, Folder 804)
  - Grand Forks Parks District Foundation - The Grand Forks Freezeway: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54734) (Box 58, Folder 805)
  - Grand Forks Chamber of Commerce - Leadership in the Grand Forks Region (2004-0278), 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 806)
  - Grantmaker Forum on Community and National Service - Philanthropies and Civic Engagement Strategies (2004-0076), 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 807-808)
  - Grandmont Rosedale Development Corporation - D1 Neighborhood Retail and Public Life (2015-51134), 2013-2015 (Box 59, Folder 815)
  - Greater Akron Amenities, Inc. - Invitations to Akron: Marketing Campaigns Targeting 18-24 Year Olds (2016-53156) (Box 59, Folder 820)
  - Greater Akron Amenities - Everything is Earned: A Plan to Attract and Retain 18-34 Year Olds (2014-49867) (Box 59, Folder 821)
  - Greater Milwaukee Committee for Community Development - Cities and Systems for the Project Economy (2015-51065), 2015-2016 (Box 59, Folder 825)
  - Greater Ohio Policy Center, Inc. - Market Rate Housing Report for Akron (2016-52940) (Box 59, Folder 826)
  - Gulf Coast Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant (2009-0253), 2009-2017 (Box 60, Folder 840)
  - Habitat for Humanity of Greater Miami - Hard Hats and High Heels (2017-54241) (Box 60, Folder 841)
  - Habitat for Humanity of Greater Miami - Knight Staff Build 2017 (2016-53611) (Box 60, Folder 842)
  - Here's My Chance - Next Stop: Democracy: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50673), 2013-2015 (Box 61, Folder 851)
  - Hialeah Public Libraries - Internet and Digital Literacy Skills (2011-0037), 2009-2012 (Box 61, Folder 852)
  - Hispanics in Philanthropy - Expand HIPGive.org (2015-50538) (Box 61, Folder 857)
  - Historic Macon Foundation Inc. - Macon Beall's Hill Revitalization: A National Model (2014-48565), 2013-2017 (Box 61, Folder 859)
  - Historic Macon Foundation Inc. - Macon Beall's Hill Revitalization: Part II (2014-48975), 2013-2016 (Box 61, Folder 860)
  - Historical Association of Southern Florida Inc. - HistoryMiami Hackathon (2014-49352) (Box 61, Folder 861)
  - Historical Association of Southern Florida Inc. - World War I: A Century Later: Origins and Legacies (2014-49479) (Box 61, Folder 862)
  - Historic Macon Foundation - The Neighborhood Incubator (2016-52776), 2016-2017 (Box 62, Folder 864)
  - Human Scale Studio, Wayne State University - The People First Project: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52493), 2014-2017 (Box 62, Folder 871)
  - Housing Trust Silicon Valley - Supporting Housing Ready Communities (2017-54164) (Box 62, Folder 872)
  - Housing Trust Silicon Valley - SV@Home (2015-50715) (Box 62, Folder 873)
  - Hunter Franks, Better Block Foundation - Innerbelt National Forest: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54192) (Box 62, Folder 875)
  - Hunter Franks - Akron Innovation Lab Artist-In-Residence (2014-50036), 2012-2015 (Box 62, Folder 876)
  - iCivics, Inc. - Connecting Young Citizens to Civic Engagements (2017-55234) (Box 62, Folder 878)
  - Ideame - idea.me "Create Miami" (2012-3186), 2012-2014 (Box 62, Folder 880)
  - Ideas42 - Using Behavioral Insights for City Success (2015-50495), 2013-2015 (Box 62, Folder 881)
  - Immigrant Legal Resource Center - New American Campaign (2017-54557), 2016-2017 (Box 63, Folder 883)
  - Immigrant Legal Resource Center - New American Campaign (2013-45496), 2013-2016 (Box 63, Folder 884)
  - Incourage Community Foundation - Interactive Resident-Driven Information Platform: 2016 KCIC Reinvestment (2016-53250), 2016-2017 (Box 63, Folder 885)
  - Incourage Community Foundation - Incourage Community Learning (2014-48271), 2011-2015 (Box 63, Folder 886)
  - Independent Sector - John W. Gardner Award Dinner, Jeff Skoll (2012-0209), 2011-2012 (Box 63, Folder 892)
  - In Our Backyards, Inc. - ioby.org Scale Up (2014-48189) (Box 63, Folder 894)
  - In Our Backyards, Inc. - St. Paul Phase 0 Research (2016-52276) (Box 63, Folder 895)
  - Institute for Commercialization of Public Research - Funding Event (2014-48204) (Box 63, Folder 896)
  - Institute for America's Future - Black Male Re-Imagined II (2013-43494), 2011-2013 (Box 64, Folder 897)
  - Institute for the Future - Open Cities Conference (2014-50208), 2013-2014 (Box 64, Folder 901)
  - International House of Metrolina, Inc. - Organizational Capacity Building (2004-0190), 2004-2005 (Box 65, Folder 914)
  - International Institute of Akron, Inc. - North Hill Neighborhood (2016-52726), 2014-2016 (Box 65, Folder 916)
  - International Women's Forum - Executive Development Roundtable Program (2016-53709) (Box 66, Folder 918)
  - International Women's Forum - Executive Development Roundtable with Miami-area Entrepreneurs (2014-50021), 2013-2015 (Box 66, Folder 919)
  - Invest Detroit Foundation - Strategic Neighborhood Fund (2016-53098), 2015-2017 (Box 66, Folder 922)
  - Invest Detroit Foundation - Partnerships and Dialogue for Ethical Redevelopment (2016-53266) (Box 66, Folder 923)
  - Island Press, Center for Resource Economics - Startup City for Code for America (2015-51528) (Box 66, Folder 932)
  - Issue Media Group - On the Ground (2015-50383) (Box 67, Folder 933)
    To attract and retain talent in Philadelphia through the creation of pop-up community media hubs.
  - Issue Media Group - Urban Innovator Exchange, Detroit (2014-49047), 2012-2014 (Box 67, Folder 934)
  - The James J. Hill Reference Library, St. Paul - Director of Programming (2016-53233) (Box 67, Folder 935)
  - Jefferson East Inc. - Civic Engagement in Changing Public Spaces (2016-53264) (Box 67, Folder 939)
  - Jefferson East Inc. - Growing Detroit's Mobility Infrastructure (2015-51809), 2012-2017 (Box 67, Folder 940)
  - Jefferson Institute - Community Software Platform and Mobile Apps (2014-50198), 2013-2014 (Box 67, Folder 941)
  - JMJ Clutch Enterprises LLC - Future Leaders of Tech II (2016-53448), 2016-2017 (Box 67, Folder 943)
  - JMJ Clutch Enterprises LLC - Wyncode Scholarships (2015-50384) (Box 67, Folder 944)
  - John Bartram Association - Expanding Bartram's Garden Civic Engagement Activities (2016-53465) (Box 67, Folder 945)
  - Johnson C. Smith University - Historic West End Event Series (2015-51494), 2015-2017 (Box 67, Folder 947)
  - Kenmore Neighborhood Alliance - Kenmore Community Development Corporation (2017-54627) (Box 68, Folder 967)
  - Kiva Microfunds - Kiva San Jose (2016-53021) (Box 69, Folder 973)